

Faculty of Engineering
The University of Sydney

E-mail: linwei.tao@sydney.edu.au Web: www.taolinwei.com Tel: (+61) 0413 002 799

Research Interest: Uncertainty Calibration, Computer Vision

Profile

Linwei Tao is going to start his Ph.D. study in University of Sydney (USYD), advised by Dr. Chang Xu. Before that, he received his B.S. degree Huazhong University of Science and Technology. His research interest lies in uncertainty calibration and computer vision. I work as TA for COMP5329 and HTIN5005 in USYD.

Personal Information

• Date of Birth: 10/09/1994

· Citizenship: China

· Language: Chinese, English

Education

- Oct 2021 Apr 2023: Masters (Research) Philosophy, The University of Sydney
- · Aug 2020 Jul 2020: Master of Data Science, The University of Sydney
- Sep 2013 Jul 2017: Communication Engineering, Bachelor of Engineering, Huazhong

University of Science and Technology

Research

L. Tao, M. Dong, D. Liu, C. Sun, C. Xu: Calibrating a Deep Neural Network with Its Predecessors, International Joint Conference on Artificial Intelligence (IJCAI), 2023.

L. Tao, M. Dong, C. Xu: Dual Focal Loss for Calibration, International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML), 2023.

Experience

Teaching Assistant, University of Sydney - Jan 2022 - Now

- COMP5329 Deep Learning Feb 2023 Jun 2023
- · COMP5329 Deep Learning Feb 2022 Jun 2022
- HTIN5005 Applied Healthcare Data Science July 2022 December 2022

Supervisor, Songjiang Construction Project Quality Supervision Station – Aug 2017 - Oct 2019

- Managed and maintained supervision parameters of construction project and data statistics website; Maintained remote monitoring system (via the webpage), mobile monitoring system (via the application)
- Supervised the progress of all unfinished Songjiang construction projects on site

Technical trainee, Trip.com – Jun 2016 - Sep 2016

- · Assisted in developing Ctrip app, IOS hotel search page, hotel details page
- · Used Object.C and Xcode to develop IOS
- Participated in the learning program organised by the company's Technology Department, to learn Java, Python, big data, and artificial intelligence.

Honour & Award

- Excellent Student Cadre of HUST, 2014
- Science and Technology Scholarship of HUST, 2014
- Smart Hardware Award, 2015